momjunction.com 2018-07-01

# Privacy Policy - MomJunction

“Privacy can be invaded” this statement describes how the personal information collected through the community when you register with us, is protected. The terms  **“we”**  and  **“us”**  refer to IncNut Digital Pvt Ltd (the parent company of MomJunction), and are part of the Terms of Use, which govern your use of the Site.

 **  INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT: **

 **Account information.**  Information that you provide us when you register, such as your name (first and last name or initial) and email id, is stored with us. If you wish to make your joining process easier you can import your information from a third party. Your email address is used to provide you services in connection with the community and contact you on behalf of other users, who would want to contact you with a message, follow and like. We may also use additional information like your gender, birth date and signup location (if you provide them) to display relevant updates and feed to you. You can change the information through the user account section of our community. ** **

 **Public content.**  You can contribute to the Site in various ways, including writing reviews, uploading videos and photos, participating in question and answers, tagging products, filling out your public profile, and voting on other users’ contributions. We may store these contributions (your ‘ **Public Content’** ), display them to other users, and use them for promotional purposes. Note that if you include personally identifiable information in your Public Content, it can be used and viewed by others. We are not responsible for the information you choose to include in your Public Content.

 **Messaging.**  The Site allows you to exchange messages with others using the messaging feature and email. We may store these messages in order to deliver them and allow you to manage them.

 **Inviting friends.**  You can invite your friends to join the Site by providing their contact information, or by entering your log-in credentials to import your address book from other sites. We may store and use your friends’ contact information to invite them to join and connect with you on the Site. Your friends will always have the opportunity to opt out of receiving further emails from us.

 **Third party services.**  We allow you to access third party services, such as Facebook and Twitter, to share your selected Public Content with those services, and import information about who you are connected with on those other services so you can connect with them on the Site. You can always opt out on your MomJunction account page. Some of those third party services may also provide us with information from your accounts to enhance and personalize your use of this Site. For example, you can allow Facebook to tell us who your Facebook friends are, so you can follow their activity on MomJunction. You may modify your privacy settings with third party services. For example, you can adjust your privacy setting on Facebook to prevent your friends from sharing information about you from their Facebook accounts with MomJunction.

 **Activity and log data.**  We automatically store information related to your use of the Site, such as the pages you view on the Site, your browser type, IP address, requested URL, browser language, referring URL, and the date and time of your visits. We use this type of information to administer the Site and provide a better service to you. We also use this information in the aggregate to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics, in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Site or to manage or improve the Site.

 **Cookies.**  We send cookies to your computer in order to uniquely identify your browser and improve the quality of our service. “Cookies” refer to small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing the Site. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). Persistent cookies can be removed by following your browser help file directions. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the Site may not work properly or at all. Our cookies are linked to your information, such as your name, email address and password. We enable some of our business partners to use cookies in conjunction with your use of the Site. We have no access to or control over the use of these cookies. These cookies collect information about your use of the Site, such as where you came from, which pages youhave visited within the Site, and possibly other sites you visit if those sites cooperate with the same third party. However, the cookies do not collect your name, email address, contact information or other personally identifiable information that by itself would allow the third party to identify or contact you.

 **Feedback.**  You can feel free to give us feedback, register a complaint, or ask questions about the Site. We may store your communications, including any personal information you include in them, so that we can effectively respond to you.

 **Administration.**  We may use the information described above for routine administrative purposes, such as investigating abuses on the Site, responding to user inquiries and enforcing and applying our Terms of Service and Statement.

 **Data storage.**  We store data in India.

 **TRANSFER OF INFORMATION:**

 **Public Content.**  If you post content for public view on the Site, we may distribute such Public Content to a wider audience by sharing it (or portions of it) with third parties so that they can publish it on their own websites and media platforms. We may ask them to credit you as the source of these contributions by including your account name and profile photo.

 **Third party service providers.**  We may use third parties to provide technical and customer support, perform tracking and reporting functions, conduct quality assurance testing, do payment processing and provide other services in connection with the Site. We may share information about you with them so that they can perform the services they are required to. But they are not permitted to use your personal information for anything other than to provide the services requested by you.

 **Third party advertising.**  Third parties serve some of the ads on the Site. We do not send any individualized personal information to them, but they may have access to information that they obtain through cookies or that you share with them yourself. Note that we do not rent, share, sell or trade personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

 **Aggregate information.**  We may share non-personal information in the aggregate to third parties relating to user behavior in connection with actual or prospective business relationship with those third parties, such as advertisers and content distributors. For example, we may disclose the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, advertising banners.

 **Business transfers.**  We may share your information with our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control that we may have now or in the future, in which case we will require them to honor this Statement. If another company acquires our company or all or substantially all of our assets, that company will possess your information, and will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information as described in this Statement.

 **Investigations.**  We reserve the right to investigate abuses on the Site, and enforce and apply our Terms of Service and Statement. We may disclose information about you to third parties if we have a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) take action regarding suspected illegal activities; (b) enforce or apply our Terms of Service and Statement; (c) comply with legal process and law enforcement instructions and orders, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on us; or (d) protect our rights, reputation, and property, or that of our users, affiliates, or the public.

 **MANAGING YOUR INFORMATION**

We provide a number of tools to manage the use of your information on the Site. You may receive weekly newsletter communications from us. However, despite any requests to close your account or your indicated email preferences, we may still need to contact you as required by law or on legal matters, for example to inform you of any updates to our Terms of Service or this Statement.

 **LINKS**

The Site may contain links to third party websites with which we have no affiliation. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your personal information with those third parties, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on all such third party websites.

 **OUR POLICY TOWARDS CHILDREN**

The Site is intended for general audiences and is not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you come to know that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at sangramsimha@incnut.com. If we come to know that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information without parental consent, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child’s account.

 **SECURITY**

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

 **INTERNET BASED ADVERTISING**

Google AdSense is used on MomJunction.com.  Adsense serves ads based on the content of the sites you view.  As you browse websites that have partnered with Google or Google sites, such as YouTube, Google may place a cookie in your browser to track the types of pages visited or content that you viewed. Based on this information, Google associates your browser with relevant interest categories and uses these categories to show interest-based ads. For example, if you frequently visit travel websites, Google may show more ads related to travel.  Google does not associate sensitive interest categories with your browser (such as those based on race, religion, sexual orientation, health, or sensitive financial categories), and does not use such categories when showing you interest-based ads.

 **How do I opt out of interest-based advertising?**  If you prefer not to receive interest-based advertising, you can click the “Opt out” button at the top of this page, or click on the “Opt out” button on the Google Ads Preferences Manager Page. Google also offers a number of options to permanently save your opt-out settings in your browser. After you opt out, Google will not collect interest category information and you will not receive interest-based ads.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie.**  Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on MomJunction.com. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to MomJunction.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

  * Google Adsense
  * Commission Junction
  * Widget Bucks
  * Adbrite
  * Clickbank
  * Azoogle
  * Chitika
  * Linkshare
  * Amazon
  * Kontera

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on MomJunction.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. MomJunction.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt out of certain practices. MomJunction.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **DISPUTE RESOLUTION**

If you believe that MomJunction has not adhered to this Statement, you may write to IncNut privacy office at the following address:

IncNut Digital Pvt Ltd  
3rd floor, Plot 12, HUDA Techno Layout  
Raj Cyber Vihar  
Hyderabad, Telangana 500081  
India

or contact us via email at [sangramsimha@incnut.com](mailto:sangramsimha@stylecraze.com)

 **MODIFICATIONS TO THIS STATEMENT**

We may revise this Statement from time to time. The most current version of the Statement will govern our use of your information and will always be located here. If we make a change to this Statement that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes, prior to implementing the change on the Site and/or via the email associated with your account. By continuing to access or use the services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Statement
“Privacy can be invaded” this statement describes how the personal information collected through the community when you register with us, is protected. The terms  **“we”**  and  **“us”**  refer to IncNut Digital Pvt Ltd (the parent company of MomJunction), and are part of the Terms of Use, which govern your use of the Site.

 **  INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT: **

 **Account information.**  Information that you provide us when you register, such as your name (first and last name or initial) and email id, is stored with us. If you wish to make your joining process easier you can import your information from a third party. Your email address is used to provide you services in connection with the community and contact you on behalf of other users, who would want to contact you with a message, follow and like. We may also use additional information like your gender, birth date and signup location (if you provide them) to display relevant updates and feed to you. You can change the information through the user account section of our community. ** **

 **Public content.**  You can contribute to the Site in various ways, including writing reviews, uploading videos and photos, participating in question and answers, tagging products, filling out your public profile, and voting on other users’ contributions. We may store these contributions (your ‘ **Public Content’** ), display them to other users, and use them for promotional purposes. Note that if you include personally identifiable information in your Public Content, it can be used and viewed by others. We are not responsible for the information you choose to include in your Public Content.

 **Messaging.**  The Site allows you to exchange messages with others using the messaging feature and email. We may store these messages in order to deliver them and allow you to manage them.

 **Inviting friends.**  You can invite your friends to join the Site by providing their contact information, or by entering your log-in credentials to import your address book from other sites. We may store and use your friends’ contact information to invite them to join and connect with you on the Site. Your friends will always have the opportunity to opt out of receiving further emails from us.

 **Third party services.**  We allow you to access third party services, such as Facebook and Twitter, to share your selected Public Content with those services, and import information about who you are connected with on those other services so you can connect with them on the Site. You can always opt out on your MomJunction account page. Some of those third party services may also provide us with information from your accounts to enhance and personalize your use of this Site. For example, you can allow Facebook to tell us who your Facebook friends are, so you can follow their activity on MomJunction. You may modify your privacy settings with third party services. For example, you can adjust your privacy setting on Facebook to prevent your friends from sharing information about you from their Facebook accounts with MomJunction.

 **Activity and log data.**  We automatically store information related to your use of the Site, such as the pages you view on the Site, your browser type, IP address, requested URL, browser language, referring URL, and the date and time of your visits. We use this type of information to administer the Site and provide a better service to you. We also use this information in the aggregate to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics, in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Site or to manage or improve the Site.

 **Cookies.**  We send cookies to your computer in order to uniquely identify your browser and improve the quality of our service. “Cookies” refer to small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing the Site. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). Persistent cookies can be removed by following your browser help file directions. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the Site may not work properly or at all. Our cookies are linked to your information, such as your name, email address and password. We enable some of our business partners to use cookies in conjunction with your use of the Site. We have no access to or control over the use of these cookies. These cookies collect information about your use of the Site, such as where you came from, which pages youhave visited within the Site, and possibly other sites you visit if those sites cooperate with the same third party. However, the cookies do not collect your name, email address, contact information or other personally identifiable information that by itself would allow the third party to identify or contact you.

 **Feedback.**  You can feel free to give us feedback, register a complaint, or ask questions about the Site. We may store your communications, including any personal information you include in them, so that we can effectively respond to you.

 **Administration.**  We may use the information described above for routine administrative purposes, such as investigating abuses on the Site, responding to user inquiries and enforcing and applying our Terms of Service and Statement.

 **Data storage.**  We store data in India.

 **TRANSFER OF INFORMATION:**

 **Public Content.**  If you post content for public view on the Site, we may distribute such Public Content to a wider audience by sharing it (or portions of it) with third parties so that they can publish it on their own websites and media platforms. We may ask them to credit you as the source of these contributions by including your account name and profile photo.

 **Third party service providers.**  We may use third parties to provide technical and customer support, perform tracking and reporting functions, conduct quality assurance testing, do payment processing and provide other services in connection with the Site. We may share information about you with them so that they can perform the services they are required to. But they are not permitted to use your personal information for anything other than to provide the services requested by you.

 **Third party advertising.**  Third parties serve some of the ads on the Site. We do not send any individualized personal information to them, but they may have access to information that they obtain through cookies or that you share with them yourself. Note that we do not rent, share, sell or trade personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

 **Aggregate information.**  We may share non-personal information in the aggregate to third parties relating to user behavior in connection with actual or prospective business relationship with those third parties, such as advertisers and content distributors. For example, we may disclose the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, advertising banners.

 **Business transfers.**  We may share your information with our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control that we may have now or in the future, in which case we will require them to honor this Statement. If another company acquires our company or all or substantially all of our assets, that company will possess your information, and will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information as described in this Statement.

 **Investigations.**  We reserve the right to investigate abuses on the Site, and enforce and apply our Terms of Service and Statement. We may disclose information about you to third parties if we have a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) take action regarding suspected illegal activities; (b) enforce or apply our Terms of Service and Statement; (c) comply with legal process and law enforcement instructions and orders, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on us; or (d) protect our rights, reputation, and property, or that of our users, affiliates, or the public.

 **MANAGING YOUR INFORMATION**

We provide a number of tools to manage the use of your information on the Site. You may receive weekly newsletter communications from us. However, despite any requests to close your account or your indicated email preferences, we may still need to contact you as required by law or on legal matters, for example to inform you of any updates to our Terms of Service or this Statement.

 **LINKS**

The Site may contain links to third party websites with which we have no affiliation. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your personal information with those third parties, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on all such third party websites.

 **OUR POLICY TOWARDS CHILDREN**

The Site is intended for general audiences and is not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you come to know that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at sangramsimha@incnut.com. If we come to know that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information without parental consent, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child’s account.

 **SECURITY**

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

 **INTERNET BASED ADVERTISING**

Google AdSense is used on MomJunction.com.  Adsense serves ads based on the content of the sites you view.  As you browse websites that have partnered with Google or Google sites, such as YouTube, Google may place a cookie in your browser to track the types of pages visited or content that you viewed. Based on this information, Google associates your browser with relevant interest categories and uses these categories to show interest-based ads. For example, if you frequently visit travel websites, Google may show more ads related to travel.  Google does not associate sensitive interest categories with your browser (such as those based on race, religion, sexual orientation, health, or sensitive financial categories), and does not use such categories when showing you interest-based ads.

 **How do I opt out of interest-based advertising?**  If you prefer not to receive interest-based advertising, you can click the “Opt out” button at the top of this page, or click on the “Opt out” button on the Google Ads Preferences Manager Page. Google also offers a number of options to permanently save your opt-out settings in your browser. After you opt out, Google will not collect interest category information and you will not receive interest-based ads.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie.**  Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on MomJunction.com. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to MomJunction.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

  * Google Adsense
  * Commission Junction
  * Widget Bucks
  * Adbrite
  * Clickbank
  * Azoogle
  * Chitika
  * Linkshare
  * Amazon
  * Kontera

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on MomJunction.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. MomJunction.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt out of certain practices. MomJunction.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **DISPUTE RESOLUTION**

If you believe that MomJunction has not adhered to this Statement, you may write to IncNut privacy office at the following address:

IncNut Digital Pvt Ltd  
3rd floor, Plot 12, HUDA Techno Layout  
Raj Cyber Vihar  
Hyderabad, Telangana 500081  
India

or contact us via email at [sangramsimha@incnut.com](mailto:sangramsimha@stylecraze.com)

 **MODIFICATIONS TO THIS STATEMENT**

We may revise this Statement from time to time. The most current version of the Statement will govern our use of your information and will always be located here. If we make a change to this Statement that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes, prior to implementing the change on the Site and/or via the email associated with your account. By continuing to access or use the services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Statement
